Guide to the David Dinkins Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Campaigns and Political Career, 1965-1994
  - Subseries I.2: Campaigns, 1965-1994
    - Mayoral, 1993
      - Local 1199 Political Action Weekend--How to Win an Election: Campaign Planning and Strategy, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Lynch, William
        - Data, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 6)
        - Views From Inside City Hall--Includes Drafts, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Mayoral Candidate Questionnaires and Responses from David Dinkins--By Topic, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 58, Folder 8 to 9)
      - Makovsky, Michael. "An Inside Story: the Jewish Vote in the 1989 New York Mayoral Election," 1991 April 5 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - The Manhattan Institute, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - March on Washington Launch--Remarks, Press Releases, Drafts and Notes, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Marist Institute for Public Opinion Polls, 1992 February, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Mayoral Campaign Expenditures and Projected Campaign Expenditures for 1993, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Mayoral Election Fact sheet, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Mayor’s Office For People with Disabilities, 1990-1993 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Mayor’s Report on Education--First Draft, 1993 September 8 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Media Briefings, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 59, Folder 10 to 11)
      - Media Briefings, 1993 March-October, (2 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Media Monitoring Guidelines, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Media, Radio and Television, 1990-1992, (2 Folders) (Box 60, Folder 4 to 5)
      - Meeting Notes, circa 1993 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - Meeting Spaces, Requests For, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Meetings With National Hispanic Business Group, Gracie Mansion, 1993 March 24 (Box 60, Folder 8)
      - Minority and Women Contractors, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - The Morning Line and the Good News, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Mosaic to Mosaic: The New York-Sarajevo Project, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - National Association of Workers, 1991-1993 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - National Association of Social Workers--Includes Speech Drafts and Notes, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - National Conference of Democratic Mayors, 1993 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - National Jewish Democratic Council, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - National Urban Policy, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - News Clippings on Rudolph Giuliani, 1992-1993 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - News Editorials and Stories, 1989, 1990-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Newsletter Proposals, 1991-1993 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - The New Yorker--Regarding the Mayoral Race, 1992-1993 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - New York City Budget, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - New York City Campaign Finance News Headlines, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - New York Citizens Committee, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - New York City Senior Bus Tour, 1993 October, (2 Folders) (Box 62, Folder 8 to 9)
      - New York County Democratic Committee, 1991-1993 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - New York League of Conservation Voters, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - New York Newsday--Clippings and Polls, 1989, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - New York State Coordinated Campaign and Field Operations, 1992 September (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - New York State Democratic Committee--Lists, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - New York State Trial Lawyers Association, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - New York Times Headlines, 1992, (2 Folders) (Box 63, Folder 5 to 6)
      - New Yorkers with Disabilities for Dinkins ’93 Committee, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 7)
      - Noble, Gil, Host of Like It Is--Summary of meeting, 1992 January (Box 63, Folder 8)
      - Older New Yorkers for Dinkins, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Op-Ed Letters--Published, 1989-1993 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Parking Violations Bureau
        - Giuliani, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 11)
        - News Clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 63, Folder 12)
      - Partnership of Faith, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 13)
      - People with Disabilities--Events, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 14)
      - Phone Bank Information, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 15)
      - Plan and Timeline for 1993--Research, Statistics and Notes, 1992-1993 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Political Planning Strategies, 1991-1993 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Polling
        - General, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 3)
        - Analysis--Comparisons, Summaries, Reports and Notes, 1984, 1988-1993, (3 Folders) (Box 64, Folder 4 to 6)
        - Statistics, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Polls
        - General, 1991-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 1 to 2)
        - Exit, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 3)
        - Latino, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 4)
        - New York Daily News, New York Newsday, New York Observer, New York Times, Marist Institute for Public Opinion and Quinnipiac College, 1989, 1992-1993, (3 Folders) (Box 65, Folder 5 to 7)
        - Surveys, statistics and News Clippings, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 1 to 2)
        - Tracking, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Positions with Drafts, 1993 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Press Releases
        - General, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 5 to 6)
        - Dinkins and Giuliani, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 66, Folder 7 to 8)
      - Primary Night, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Procedure for Review of Campaign Contributions, 1991-1993 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Profile of Registered Hispanic Voters, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Public Opinion and Voter Preferences in the 1993 New York City Mayoral Race, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Quality of Life, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Questions for Dinkins’ April 11th Interview, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Racial Issues in the 1993 Mayoral Campaign, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Race Relations--Remarks and Clippings, 1990-1993 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Rallies, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Rapid Response Releases and the Morning Line, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Rebuttal to Media Offensives, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Ten Reasons Why Mayor Dinkins Should Be Reelected, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Remarks of Mayor Dinkins at Various Events, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 67, Folder 13 to 14)
      - Research
        - Aging, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 1)
        - Committee and Budget, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 2)
        - Opposition, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 3)
        - Statistics, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 4)
        - Zionism and Racism, 1991 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Republican Record, 1992 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Republicans for Dinkins, 1993 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Scheduling Requests and Updates, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Senior Citizen Literature and Organizations, 1990-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 69, Folder 3 to 4)
      - Senior Citizens Speaker Bureau, 1992-1993 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Sierra Club
        - Candidate Interview-Format, Research and Notes, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 6)
        - City Council Questionnaire--Drafts, Notes and Research, 1989-1993 (Box 69, Folder 7)
        - City Council Questionnaire--Drafts, Notes and Research, 1989-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Sign Language Interpreters, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Small Business, 1992-1993 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Smoke Free Educational Services, Inc., 1993 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Speeches
        - General-- 1993 March-October, (3 Folders) (Box 70, Folder 6 to 8)
        - Chamber of Commerce, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 1)
        - Citizens Budget Commission, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 2)
        - Compilation of, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 3)
        - Crown Heights, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 4)
        - Drafts, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 5)
        - Endorsements, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 6 to 7)
        - Inaugural 1990 Address--Notes, 1990, 1993, undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
        - Latino Events, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 9)
        - Police Hiring, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 10)
        - South Africa and Rome--Includes Itinerary, 1991 November, (2 Folders) (Box 71, Folder 11 to 12)
        - Spring Gala at Ellis Island, 1993 May 11 (Box 71, Folder 13)
        - Volunteer Rally, 1993 (Box 71, Folder 14)
      - Staffing--Administrative, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - State of the City
        - Accomplishments, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 2)
        - Address, 1993 January 4-5 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Staten Island
        - Issues and Accomplishments, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 4)
        - Secession, 1992-1993 (Box 72, Folder 5)
        - Week, 1992 August (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Stein, Andrew
        - Attacks and Campaign Responses--Includes Stein’s Policy Book, 1988, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 72, Folder 7 to 8)
        - Letter to Gay and Lesbian Community Attacking Dinkins, 1993 (Box 72, Folder 9)
        - News Clippings, 1990-1993, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 1 to 2)
      - Stop the Violence Fund, 1991-1993 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Street Vending Initiatives, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Students for Dinkins, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Surrogates Request Forms--Events, 1993, (2 Folders) (Box 73, Folder 6 to 7)
      - Surrogate Request Forms--Events, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Surrogate Speakers, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Survey of New York City Residents, The Commonwealth Fund Improving the Quality of Life in New York City, 1993 September (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Talking Points, 1990-1993 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Transportation, 1992-1993 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Unemployment, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Various Questionnaires for Mayoral Candidates--Includes Responses, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Veterans for Dinkins, 1992-1993 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Vision for the City’s Future, 1993 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Voice of Bay Ridge Business Candidates Forum, 1993 September 30 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Volunteers
        - General, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 1)
        - Agendas, Resumes and Notes, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 2)
        - By Constituency--Lists, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
        - Committee for David Dinkins--Fact Sheets, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 4)
        - Kick-Off Rally, 1993 May 31 (Box 75, Folder 5)
        - Plan, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 6)
      - Voter Registration
        - Non-Parisian, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 7)
        - Project, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 8)
        - Research and Advertisements, 1992-1993 (Box 75, Folder 9)
      - Voting Patterns for 1989 Election, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 10)
      - Wilson, Basil. "David Dinkins and the Goliaths of New York City: The Mayoral Campaign," undated (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Women for David Dinkins, 1990-1993 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Pins--Campaigns and Pins Not Related to Dinkins Campaigns, 1985, 1989, 1993, undated (Box 76)
  - Subseries I.3: Manhattan Borough President, 1981-1993
    Subseries I.3: Manhattan Borough President, 1981-1993, is made up of primarily speeches and subject files. The subject files are organizations and typically consist of histories and general background information, newsletters and pamphlets. The topics of the speeches include, African-Americans, awards, Black and Jewish relations, budget, education, housing, and tributes. These records are photocopies with the exception of the organizational files.
    - Citations, 1988-1989 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1986-1988 (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Congratulations, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Director of the New York State Urban Development Corporation--Nomination, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Recommendations, 1985-1989 (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Regrets, 1986-1989 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Organizations
      - Adopt a Highway Program--New York City Department of Transportation, undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
      - African American Images, undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
      - The African American Institute, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 3)
      - African Street Festival--History, undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
      - Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 5)
      - Alvin Ailey American Dance Company--History, undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
      - Association of Minority Enterprises of New York (AMENY), 1992 (Box 78, Folder 7)
      - American Baptist Churches of Metropolitan New York, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 8)
      - American Cancer Society, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 9)
      - American Foundation for AIDS Research (AmFAR)--History, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - American Friends of the Hebrew University, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - American Friends of Jamaica, 1987-1988 (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - The American Indian Community House, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 13)
      - American Institute of Architects, undated (Box 78, Folder 14)
      - America-Israel Friendship League, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 15)
      - American Jewish Committee, undated (Box 78, Folder 16)
      - Appeal of Conscience Foundation, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 17)
      - Apollo Theatre, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - The Art Commission of the City of New York, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 19)
      - Arthur Ashe Tennis Challenge, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 20)
      - Asian American Legal Defense and Education Fund, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 21)
      - Associated Black Charities, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 22)
      - Association for a Better New York (ABNY), 1990 (Box 78, Folder 23)
      - Aunt Len’s Doll and Toy Museum, undated (Box 78, Folder 24)
      - Battery Park City Authority, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 25)
      - Bay Ridge Community Council, 1992 (Box 78, Folder 26)
      - Bedford Stuyvesant Community Conference, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 27)
      - Beth Israel Medical Center, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 28)
      - Big Brothers Inc. of New York City, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 29)
      - Black Arts National Diaspora, Inc., 1988 (Box 78, Folder 30)
      - Black History Month, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 31)
      - Black Veterans for Social Justice, Inc., 1989 (Box 78, Folder 32)
      - Black United Fund of New York, 1993 (Box 78, Folder 33)
      - Anti-Defamation League of B’nai B’rith, undated (Box 78, Folder 34)
      - Borden Avenue Veterans Residence, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 35)
      - Boys Choir of Harlem--History, undated (Box 78, Folder 36)
      - Bridge Street Church, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      - The Brooklyn Museum, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      - The Brooklyn Army Terminal, undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
      - Brooklyn Neighborhood Improvement Association, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 4)
      - The Bronx Museum of the Arts, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 5)
      - Bryant Park Restoration Corporation, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 6)
      - Building Owners’ and Managers’ Association of Greater New York, Inc., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 7)
      - Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 8)
      - Carnegie Hall--History, 1991 (Box 79, Folder 9)
      - Carver Federal Savings Bank--History, undated (Box 79, Folder 10)
      - Caribbean Cultural Center--History, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 11)
      - Cathedral of St. John the Divine, undated (Box 79, Folder 12)
      - Catholic Interracial Council of New York, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 13)
      - Central Baptist Church, Inc., 1988 (Box 79, Folder 14)
      - Central Brooklyn Coordinating Council, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 15)
      - Central Park Conservancy, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 16)
      - The Center for Puerto Rican Studies, undated (Box 79, Folder 17)
      - Children’s Defense Fund, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 18)
      - Charles H. Revson Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 79, Folder 19)
      - Children’s Health Fund, undated (Box 79, Folder 20)
      - Children’s Museum of Manhattan, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 21)
      - The Children’s Storefront, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 22)
      - Childs Memorial Temple Church of God in Christ, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 23)
      - Citicorp/Citibank, undated (Box 79, Folder 24)
      - The City Club, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 25)
      - City Harvest, Inc., undated (Box 79, Folder 26)
      - City of New York Department of Corrections, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 27)
      - The Graduate School and University Center the City University of New York, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 28)
      - City Volunteer Corps, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 29)
      - Citizens Energy Corporation, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 30)
      - Civil Liberties Organization--History, undated (Box 79, Folder 31)
      - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 32)
      - Colgate, undated (Box 79, Folder 33)
      - Columbia University Law School--Paul Robeson Scholarship, undated (Box 79, Folder 34)
      - Congressional Black Caucus Foundation, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 35)
      - Comic Relief Organization, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 36)
      - Committee for Hispanic Children and Families, Inc.--History, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 37)
      - The Commonwealth Fund, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 38)
      - Communications for the Progressive Community, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 39)
      - Community Service Society of New York, undated (Box 80, Folder 1)
      - Concord Baptist Church of Christ, 1992 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      - Con Edison, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 3)
      - Mayor’s Office of Contracts, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 4)
      - The Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 5)
      - CORO, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 6)
      - Council on Fiscal and Economic Priorities, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
      - Council of Jewish Organizations of Flatbush, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 8)
      - Council of Supervisors and Administrators, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 9)
      - Council on Foreign Relations, 1988-1989 (Box 80, Folder 10)
      - Covenant House, undated (Box 80, Folder 11)
      - Cultural Crossroads, Inc., 1992 (Box 80, Folder 12)
      - Credit Lyonnais--History, 1990 (Box 80, Folder 13)
      - The Dalton School, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 14)
      - Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 15)
      - Daytop Village, Inc., 1992 (Box 80, Folder 16)
      - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority--New York Alumnae Chapter, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 17)
      - Democratic National Committee, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 18)
      - The Dome Project, Inc.--History, 1991 (Box 80, Folder 19)
      - Dominican Tourist Information Center, Inc., 1992 (Box 80, Folder 20)
      - The Door, A Center of Alternatives, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 1)
      - Eastern Tennis Association, 1992 (Box 81, Folder 2)
      - The Edges Group, Inc., 1989 (Box 81, Folder 3)
      - El Museo Del Barrio, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
      - The Eldridge Street Project, undated (Box 81, Folder 5)
      - English Plus Information Clearinghouse (EPIC), 1991 (Box 81, Folder 6)
      - Federation of Italian-American Organizations of Brooklyn, undated (Box 81, Folder 7)
      - The Federation of Negro Civil Service Organization, Inc., 1989 (Box 81, Folder 8)
      - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, Inc., 1989 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      - Foreign Policy Association, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 10)
      - The Fortune Society, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 11)
      - Foundation for Child Development, 1987-1988 (Box 81, Folder 12)
      - Fountain House, Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 81, Folder 13)
      - France--History of Country, undated (Box 81, Folder 14)
      - The Friars Club, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 15)
      - Fund for the City of New York, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 16)
      - The Fund for New York City Public Education, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 17)
      - Galeries Lafayette, 1991 (Box 81, Folder 18)
      - The Garden Club of America, 1990 (Box 81, Folder 19)
      - God’s Love We Deliver, Inc., 1990 (Box 81, Folder 20)
      - Greater Harlem Real Estate Board, Inc., 1987 (Box 81, Folder 21)
      - Gracie Mansion Conservancy, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 22)
      - Graduate School of Management and Urban Policy, New School for Social Research, 1992-1993 (Box 81, Folder 23)
      - Greek American Labor Council, 1993 (Box 81, Folder 24)
      - Greenwich House Music School, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 25)
      - The Guardians Association, Inc., 1988 (Box 81, Folder 26)
      - Hale House Center, 1988-1989 (Box 81, Folder 27)
      - Harbor Festival Foundation, Inc., 1992 (Box 81, Folder 28)
      - Hamilton-Madison House, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 29)
      - Hellenic American Neighborhood Action Committee, Inc., 1990 (Box 81, Folder 30)
      - Hands Across New York, undated (Box 81, Folder 31)
      - Keith Haring Foundation, Inc., 1990 (Box 81, Folder 32)
      - Harlem Junior Tennis Program, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 1)
      - Henry Street Settlement, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Highbridge-Woodycrest Center, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 3)
      - Hispanic Link News Service Inc., 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 4)
      - Histadrut: National Committee for Labor Israel, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 5)
      - The Home Insurance Company, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 6)
      - Hospital Association of New York State, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 7)
      - Housing and Services, Inc., 1988 (Box 82, Folder 8)
      - Housing for People, Inc. (HOPE), 1988 (Box 82, Folder 9)
      - Howard University--History, undated (Box 82, Folder 10)
      - The Hundred Year Association of New York, Inc., 1993 (Box 82, Folder 11)
      - Impact II, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 12)
      - Incarnation Children’s Center, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 13)
      - Church of the Intercession, undated (Box 82, Folder 14)
      - International Gay and Lesbian Human Rights Commission, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 15)
      - International Radio and Television Society--History, undated (Box 82, Folder 16)
      - Iona College--History, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 17)
      - JVC Jazz Program, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 18)
      - Jackie Robinson Foundation, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 19)
      - Jamaica--Overview, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 20)
      - Japanese Chamber of Commerce and Industry of New York, Inc., 1990 (Box 82, Folder 21)
      - Jewish National Fund (JNF), undated (Box 82, Folder 22)
      - The Jefferson Awards, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 23)
      - Job Development Authority (JDA), 1991 (Box 82, Folder 24)
      - The Jewish Teachers Association, 1989 (Box 82, Folder 25)
      - The Joseph Papp Public Theater, 1992 (Box 82, Folder 26)
      - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation International, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 27)
      - New York City Partnership, Inc., undated (Box 82, Folder 28)
      - New York College of Podiatric Medicine, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - New York County Medical Society, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - The Council of Churches of the City of New York, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 3)
      - New York Foundation for Senior Citizens, Inc., 1991 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - New York Junior Tennis League, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - New York Lawyers for the Public Interest, 1991 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - New York Philharmonic, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - The New York Public Library, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - New York Convention and Visitors Bureau, Inc., 1993 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - The New York Hispanic Housing Coalition, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - New York State African American Political Action Committee, undated (Box 83, Folder 11)
      - New York State Court Officers Association, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 12)
      - New York State Jewelers Association, Inc., undated (Box 83, Folder 13)
      - New York State Martin Luther King, Jr. Commission, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - New York State New Democratic Coalition, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - New York State Urban Development Corporation, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - New York Urban Coalition, 1990 (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - New York Urban League, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 18)
      - New York State International Partnership Program, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 19)
      - The Committee for a Positive Northeast Bronx, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - North Bronx Community Democratic Club, 1989 (Box 83, Folder 21)
      - One Hundred Black Men, Inc., 1990 (Box 83, Folder 22)
      - Organization of African Unity (OAU), 1990 (Box 83, Folder 23)
      - Panel of Americans, Inc., 1989 (Box 83, Folder 24)
      - Phoenix House Foundation, Inc., 1992 (Box 83, Folder 25)